Where are you going to spend your holidays this year, Gary?
Gary,今年你们打算去哪里度假?
We may go abroad.
我们可能到国外去,
I'm not sure.
但我不敢肯定.
My wife wants to go to Egypt.
我妻子想到埃及去,
I'd like to go there, too.
我也想去那儿.
We can't make up our minds.
我们还拿不定主意.
Will you travel by sea or by air?
你们乘船去,还是乘飞机去?
We may travel by sea.
我们可能乘船去.
It's cheaper, isn't it?
这更便宜些,不是吗?
I'm sure you'll enjoy yourselves.
我肯定你们一定会玩得很愉快.
Don't be so sure.
别那么肯定.
We might not go anywhere.
我们可能哪里也去不成.
My wife always worries too much.
我妻子总是担心这担心那的.
Who's going to look after the dog?
谁来照看狗啦,
Who's going to look after the house?
谁来看管房子啦,
Who's going to look after the garden?
谁来照料花园啦,
We have this problem every year.
我们每年都碰到这个问题.
In the end, we stay at home and look after everything!
最后,我们呆在家里来照看一切.